japanesevehicles.com 2018-08-20

# Privacy Statement. JapaneseVehicles.com

Home \- Privacy Statement

## Privacy Policy of JapaneseVehicles.com

Data Controller and Owner  
Trust Co. Ltd. - 3/F, Sakae VT Bldg, 3-10-32 Nishiki, Naka-ku - 460-0003 - Nagoya, JAPAN  
EMAIL: [sales@JapaneseVehicles.com](mailto:sales@JapaneseVehicles.com)

### Types of Data collected

Among the types of Personal Data that JapaneseVehicles.com collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookie, Usage Data, Phone number, Email, First Name, Last Name, Country, City, Geographic position, Genre, Address, Username, Password, Company name and Fax number.

Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.  
The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using JapaneseVehicles.com.  
Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by JapaneseVehicles.com or by the owners of third party services used by JapaneseVehicles.com, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.  
Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for JapaneseVehicles.com to provide its services.

The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through JapaneseVehicles.com and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving Trust Co. Ltd. of all responsibility. 

* * *

### Mode and place of processing the Data

##### Method of processing

Trust Co. Ltd. processes the Data of Users in proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to Trust Co. Ltd., in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Trust Co. Ltd. The updated list of these parties may be requested from Trust Co. Ltd. at any time. 

##### Place

The Data is processed at Trust Co. Ltd.'s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact Trust Co. Ltd.. 

##### Conservation Time

The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request Trust Co. Ltd. for their suspension or removal. 

* * *

### The use of the collected Data

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Website to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics, Contacting the User, Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting, Interaction with external social networks and platforms, Location-based interactions, Managing email addresses and sending messages and Registration and authentication. 

The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document. 

* * *

### Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services: 

#### Selling goods and services online

The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell goods, including payment and possible delivery.  
The Personal Data can be shared with Partners or Third Parties for the purposes of sale follow-up, shipping and clearing goods, after sale services. 

#### Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior. 

##### Google Analytics (Google)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of JapaneseVehicles.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. 

##### GoogleAdwordsconversion tracking (Google)

Google AdWords conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google, Inc. that connects data from the Google AdWords advertising network with actions performed on JapaneseVehicles.com.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. 

#### Contacting the User

##### Phone contact (JapaneseVehicles.com)

Users that provided their phone number might be contacted for commercial or promotional purposes related to JapaneseVehicles.com, as well as for fulfilling support requests.  
Personal Data collected: Phone number. 

##### Mailing List or Newsletter (JapaneseVehicles.com)

By registering to the mailing list or to the newsletter, the User`s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning JapaneseVehicles.com. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to JapaneseVehicles.com or after performing a purchase.  
Personal Data collected: City, Country, Email, First Name, Last Name and Usage Data. 

#### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

These services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of JapaneseVehicles.com.  
The interaction and information obtained by JapaneseVehicles.com are always subject to the User`s privacy settings for each social network.  
If a service enabling interaction with social networks is installed it may still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it. 

#### Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook)

The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook Inc.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. 

#### Location-based interactions

##### Geolocation (JapaneseVehicles.com)

JapaneseVehicles.com may collect and use User location Data in order to provide location-based services.  
Most browsers and devices provide tools to opt out from this feature by default. If explicit authorization has been provided, the User`s location data may be tracked by JapaneseVehicles.com.  
Personal Data collected: Geographic position. 

#### Managing email addresses and sending messages

These services make it possible to manage a database of email contacts to communicate with the User via email.  
The services are used to collect data concerning the date and time when the mail is viewed by the User, as well as when the User interacts with incoming mail, such as by clicking on links included in the email. 

#### Registration and authentication

By registering or authenticating, Users allow JapaneseVehicles.com to identify them and give them access to dedicated services. 

##### Direct registration (JapaneseVehicles.com)

The User registers by filling out the registration form and providing the Personal Data directly to JapaneseVehicles.com.  
Personal Data collected: Address, City, Company name, Country, Email, Fax number, First Name, Genre, Last Name, Password, Phone number and Username. 

#### Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting

These services allow JapaneseVehicles.com and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of JapaneseVehicles.com by the User.  
This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using Cookies, information that is transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity. 

##### Remarketing through Google Analyticsfor Display Advertising (Google)

Google Analyticsfor Display Advertising is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google Inc. that connects the tracking activity performed by Google Analytics and its Cookies with the Adwords advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. 

##### AdWords Remarketing (Google)

AdWords Remarketing is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google Inc. that connects the activity of JapaneseVehicles.com with theAdwordsadvertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie.  
Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. 

* * *

### Additional information about Data collection and processing

#### Legal Action

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by Trust Co. Ltd., in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of JapaneseVehicles.com or the related services. 

#### Additional Information about User's Personal Data

In addition to the information in this privacy policy, JapaneseVehicles.com may provide the User with contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data. 

#### System Logs and Maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, JapaneseVehicles.com and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with JapaneseVehicles.com (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address). 

#### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from Trust Co. Ltd. at any time at its contact information. 

#### The rights of Users

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult Trust Co. Ltd. to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to Trust Co. Ltd. at the contact information set out above. 

#### Changes to this privacy policy

Trust Co. Ltd. reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using JapaneseVehicles.com and can request Trust Co. Ltd. to erase the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data Trust Co. Ltd. has about Users. 

#### Information about this privacy policy

Trust Co. Ltd. is responsible for this privacy policy, prepared starting from the modules provided by Iubenda. 

* * *

### Definitions and legal references

##### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number. 

##### Usage Data

Information collected automatically from JapaneseVehicles.com (or third party services employed in JapaneseVehicles.com ), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use JapaneseVehicles.com, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment. 

##### User

The individual using JapaneseVehicles.com, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refer. 

##### Data Subject

The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers to. 

##### Data Processor

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by Trust Co. Ltd. to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy. 

##### JapaneseVehicles.com

The website by which the User Personal Data is collected. 

##### Cookie

Small piece of data stored in the User's device. 

This privacy policy is solely about JapaneseVehicles.com.   
Latest update: June 1, 2015
